

GAME DESIGNER

### **Details**

Av. Villazon Km 4 1/2, Cochabamba, Bolivia +591 72787515 kevin031995@gmail.com

### Links

<u>Portfolio</u>

Itch.io Page

### Skills

Game Development

Game Design

Critical thinking and problem solving

Communication

Ability to Work in a Team

Unity 3D

**Manual Testing** 

**Automated Testing** 

## Languages

English

Spanish

### **Hobbies**

Gaming, Drawing, Animation.

### **Profile**

Passionate part-time/hobbyist game developer with more than 5 years developing games, Experienced quality assurance engineer with 3 years of testing,

As a game developer, I have worked on commercial and hobby projects for mobile and PC platforms, covering almost all the game development process like: prototyping, work planning, task creation and assignment, programming, design, testing, and deployment to stores.

As a tester, I have worked planning and executing test plans, communicating with clients and teammates to make sure the expected requirements are clear and tested on time.

# **Employment History**

### Staff Advanced QA at Oktana Corporation, Remote

SEPTEMBER 2020 — PRESENT

- Daily meetings, Sprint Planning meetings, Retrospective meetings.
- Working with a team of up to 6 members.
- Issue track and Project Planning using Salesforce GUS.
- Regression testing before and after product releases.
- Write and execute manual tests for Salesforce products.
- Testing and Follow up of customer issues.

## Junior Automation QA at Jalasoft, Cochabamba - Bolivia

SEPTEMBER 2018 — AUGUST 2020

- Ownership of features on QA side.
- Planning, writing and executing testing to cover feature requirements on time.
- · Training of new QA members.
- Daily, Sprint Planning and Retrospective meetings, within a team of up to 18 members.
- Bitbucket(Git) merge, rebase, create and review pull requests.
- · Issue track and Testing Planning using Jira.
- Manual and Automation web/rest testing using Selenium, Postman, Excel.
- Deploy of back-end/front-end test environments using Linux, Docker.

# Unity 3D Programmer at Xiara Studios, La Paz - Bolivia

 ${\sf MARCH~2016-JANUARY~2018}$ 

- Sprint Planning and Daily meetings within a team up to 10 members using Trello
- Github merge, rebase, create and review pull requests.
- Programming Gameplay and Multiplayer Features for 2D Fighting game for Android Platforms.
- 2D assets integration with code.
- · 2D animations for characters.

## **Education**

Quality Automation Training Program, Fundacion JALA, Cochabamba

JANUARY 2018 — SEPTEMBER 2018

High School Diploma, Puerto de Mejillones, Cochabamba

JANUARY 2008 — DECEMBER 2012